<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<T3locallang>
	<meta type="array">
		<description>CSH for alternative Page Module</description>
		<type>CSH</type>
		<csh_table>_MOD_web_txtemplavoilaM1</csh_table>
		<fileId>EXT:templavoila/locallang_csh_pm.xml</fileId>
	</meta>
	<data type="array">
		<languageKey index="default" type="array">
			<label index="pagemodule.alttitle">Page Module (TemplaVoilà)</label>
			<label index="pagemodule.description">The TemplaVoilà Page Module lets you easily edit content of your web page. You see the content fitted according to the layout of how it is displayed in the frontend.</label>
			<label index="pagemodule_notUsed.description">Lists all elements that are added but not visually linked (and therefore not displayed) to this page. Usually these elements were unlinked (using the trash icon below) but are not completely deleted yet. Once you are sure </label>
			<label index="selectlanguageversion.description">By selecting a specific language, you can narrow down the output of the page module. Use this option in conjunction with the display mode option 'Selected Language' below.</label>
			<label index="editlanguageversion.description">Every translation of a page has its own page title, keywords or other meta information. Click on the corresponding flag to edit this information for a specific language. If a flag of a translation that you want to translate does not show up, you maybe need to create a new translation first.</label>
			<label index="createnewtranslation.description">Select the appropriate flag to create a new translation for this page. Once the language is added, you can translate the page properties and start translating the page content of the original page.</label>
			<label index="pagelocalizationmode.description">You can see here how the page is localized. Translations either allow separate structures (more flexible) or stick to a 1:1 translation (only translate elements in the default language). This setting is defined in the Data Structure source of the Page Template.</label>
			<label index="pagelocalizationdisplaymode.description">The display mode lets you switch between displaying all languages, only the selected language that you chose in the select box above, or only the elements that were translated already. Where the first option gives you a nice overview of all elements that are translated yet, you can focus on one language by displaying only the selected translation page and / or elements.</label>
			<label index="advancedfunctions_showhiddenelements.description">Enabling this option also displays the content elements that are hidden in the </label>
			<label index="advancedfunctions_showoutline.description">This display mode shows the data structures of the elements that are used in this page. It is mainly used for administration purposes and to clean up the XML if something went wrong on this page.</label>
			<label index="outline_status_cleanall.description">[FILL IN]Why is my XML dirty and why do I want to clean it up?</label>
		</languageKey>
	</data>
</T3locallang>
