<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<T3locallang>
	<meta type="array">
		<description>Language file for TV template settings</description>
		<type>module</type>
		<csh_table></csh_table>
		<fileId>EXT:templavoila/res1/language/template_conf.xml</fileId>
		<labelContext type="array">
		</labelContext>
	</meta>
	<data type="array">
		<languageKey index="default" type="array">
			<label index="enable.oldPageModule">Enable the classic Page module:Check this box to enable classic Page module in the list of modules.</label>
			<label index="enable.selectDataStructure">Enable data structure selection: If this checkbox is checked, page and content elements will have data structure selector as they had in older TemplaVoila versions. If current installation has very few template objects, it is recommended to have this checkbox unchecked.</label>
			<label index="enable.renderFCEHeader">Enable Header for FCE's:If this checkbox is checked the header of Content Element type FCE will be rendered like headers of other Content Elements.</label>
			<label index="staticDS.enable">Enable static files for data structures:Experimental! Use Static DS Conversion Wizard below!</label>
			<label index="staticDS.path_fce">FCE Data Structure Path:Path to the static data structures for flexible content elements</label>
			<label index="staticDS.path_page">Page Data Structure Path:Path to the static data structures for pages</label>
			<label index="staticDS.wizard">Static DS Conversion Wizard</label>
			<label index="staticDS.wizard.uid">UID</label>
			<label index="staticDS.wizard.pid">PID</label>
			<label index="staticDS.wizard.title">Title</label>
			<label index="staticDS.wizard.scope">Scope</label>
			<label index="staticDS.wizard.usage">Usage</label>
			<label index="staticDS.wizard.selectall">select/deselect all</label>
			<label index="staticDS.wizard.title.0">Check data structure paths</label>
			<label index="staticDS.wizard.description.0">The wizard checks if the data structure paths exist and are writeable. If a path does not exist, it attempts to create the necessary directory.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you want to update your records, ensure you checked "staticDS.enable" before starting the wizard.</label>
			<label index="staticDS.wizard.title.1">Convert existing data structures</label>
			<label index="staticDS.wizard.description.1">This step copies your existing data structures into static files using the specified data structure paths. Static files that already exist will be overwritten.&lt;br /&gt;Since the existing data structures remain unchanged, this is also an easy way to back up data structure records without actually using the static data structure functionality.</label>
			<label index="staticDS.wizard.description2.1">Are you sure you want to enable static data structures? This feature is experimental and it is recommended that you perform a database backup of all tables involved (pages, tt_content, tx_templavoila_datastructure, and tx_templavoila_tmplobj) before continuing.</label>
			<label index="staticDS.wizard.dircheck.ok">Directory "%s"  exists and is writable. Ready for usage.</label>
			<label index="staticDS.wizard.dircheck.notok">&lt;strong&gt;Error:&lt;/strong&gt; Directory "%s"   could not be created or is not writable!</label>
			<label index="staticDS.wizard.dircheck.notset">&lt;strong&gt;Setting:&lt;/strong&gt; "%s" missing. Please check and update the existing configuration.</label>
			<label index="staticDS.wizard.submit1">static DS Wizard - Step 1: Check paths</label>
			<label index="staticDS.wizard.submit2">static DS Wizard - Step 2: Copy your existing data structures to files</label>
			<label index="staticDS.wizard.submit3">static DS Wizard - Step 2: Update database records and enable static data structures</label>
			<label index="staticDS.wizard.updaterecords">Update database records and enable static data structure</label>
			<label index="staticDS.wizard.updated">All tables were updated, Templavoila now is ready to work with created static data structure files.</label>
			<label index="staticDS.wizard.clearcache">You have to clear the configuration cache for reading the new data structures!</label>
			
		</languageKey>
	</data>
</T3locallang>
